<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hongyan Xue</title>
    <link>https://xuehongyanl.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hongyan Xue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:44:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xuehongyanl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[KDD 2023] Generating Synergistic Formulaic Alpha Collections via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://xuehongyanl.github.io/posts/kdd2023alphamining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuehongyanl.github.io/posts/kdd2023alphamining/</guid>
      <description>Shuo Yu*, Hongyan Xue*, Xiang Ao, Feiyang Pan, Jia He, Dandan Tu and Qing He
Accepted by KDD 2023 Applied Data Science (ADS) track.
[ArXiv] [GitHub] [知乎]
Abstract Link to heading In the field of quantitative trading, it is common practice to transform raw historical stock data into indicative signals for the market trend. Such signals are called alpha factors. Alphas in formula forms are more interpretable and thus favored by practitioners concerned with risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://xuehongyanl.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 11:14:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuehongyanl.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a third year PhD student, under the supervision of Prof. Qing He in the Machine Learning and Data Mining group, Key Laboratory of Intelligent Information Processing, Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences (MLDM, IIP, ICT, CAS). [简历PDF].
Education Link to heading Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences (ICT, CAS), 2021-now Direct doctoral student University of Chinese Academy of Sciences (UCAS), 2017-2021 Received B.E. of computer science Research Interests Link to heading I am working on some subfields related to Reinforcement Learning:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://xuehongyanl.github.io/posts/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 11:10:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuehongyanl.github.io/posts/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>Hello world! Link to heading TODO</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
